Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Hans Weissenstein Negatives PHOTOS 019 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Individuals
  - Ernest] Fleishman Portraits [Collection includes two corresponding prints.], Apr 28, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9237)
  - Rae Fraenkel [headshots], Oct 14, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13530)
  - QuEST Course Gramercy Park Hotel, Ray Frank, Nov 11, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13619)
  - PAC Freeman [seated with others], Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13845)
  - Paul Gershaw, Jun 21, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11978)
  - Reading Classes PS 130 Bronx Paul Gershwin, May 17, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13311)
  - Teacher of the Year Paul Gershwin[?], Bronx, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13575)
  - Pension Bernie [?] Goldberg [?], Oct 3, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12080)
  - District 22 Peter Goodman, Feb 4, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11643)
  - Senator Ray Goodman, Dec 22, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13772)
  - [Allen] Griggs Portrait, Jan 24, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9602)
  - Citizen Council for the Handicapped - Gramercy Hotel - Sid Harris, Oct 13, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13527)
  - Board of Education Handicapped Awards Sid Harris, May 19, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12609)
  - Brotherhood in Action Sid Harris, 560 7th Ave., Nov 5, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13603)
  - Sid Harris - Rep. [?] Children Olymp. [?] Brass Rail, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13270)
  - Board of Education Sid Harris, Jun 10, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11956)
  - Board of Education PS 207 PS Retarded Children Sid Harris, Apr 21, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12529)
  - Lou Hert, Kansas City PS 146 + UFT, Nov 14, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12200)
  - Demonstration Para-Professional John Hill, District 5 Manhattan, Sep 14, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13476)
  - Secretaries / Voc. H. S. / John Hill, Oct 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12113)
  - Board of Education Demonstration Brooklyn John Hill, Oct 15, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13534)
  - Haaren HS NYC Mini school John Hill, Oct 15, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13533)
  - John Hill posing, Apr 9, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13200)
  - District Reps. Lecture - John Hill - Sandy Feldman - [David] Wittes, Sep 22, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12063)
  - PS 179 Queens Velma Hill, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13801)
  - JHS 232 Brooklyn - Program of Living Witness - Velma Hill, Feb 8, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13828)
  - Velma Hill Workmen's Circle, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13844)
  - PS 332 Brooklyn meeting Velma Hill, Jan 7, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13785)
  - Para-Professional - Velma Hill - Elected Reps - Marc Ballroom, Jun 18, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13412)
  - Roosevelt HS Velma Hill: World of Work Program 70 [?] Central Labor Council, Mar 22, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13158)
  - Hillcrest [classroom], Sep 27, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13490)
  - Ponce [Ponsie?] Hillman [headshots], May 27, 1970 (Box 30, Item 15602)
  - JHS 271 Brooklyn Ponsie Hillman, Apr 12, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14305)
  - Senator Hobson - Manhattan Office, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13771)
  - PS 134 Queens w/ A. L. Hollis Open House, May 14, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13298)
  - [John J.] Holub, undated (Box 6, Item 10731)
  - Doris Hunter PS-25 Para-Professional, Mar 10, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12429)
  - PS 25 Julia Rogers - Doris Hunter, Jun 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11969)
  - Doris Hunter [headshots], Feb 28, 1970 (Box 30, Item 15599)
  - Sol Jaffe Portraits [Negative is missing; only photographic print remains.], Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9869)
  - AFT Banquet Senator Jacob K. Javits & Joe Adams, Aug 22, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7825)
  - Ben Kaplan Portraits [Collection includes a corresponding print.], Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9864)
  - Eugene Kaufman [Legal] Council, Mar 10, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11705)
  - Coop City Ass. [?] Board, Israel Bonds, Eugene Kaufman, Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13870)
  - Robert F. Kennedy Commodore Hotel, Oct 31, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8637)
  - PS 181 Anne Kessler - Instructing, Jan 27, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13036)
  - District 4 - Bill Kilgour (Kenneth Weissman incumbent), Feb 27, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11684)
  - Mrs. Kimbel PS 76 LIC Queens, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13504)
  - Klein, Max, Nov 23, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10164)
  - PP-PS-33 Mrs. Pearl Klonsky, Mar 9, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12426)
  - [Mildred] Klotz, Jan 23, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10253)
  - Congressman [Edward] Koch (Federal Plaza), Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13578)
  - [Jules] Kolodny - [Eugene] Molloy [Monsignor] Debate, Jan 22, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10256)
  - Fordham University Panel [Jules Kolodny speaking], Jun 20, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14070)
  - Board of Education Budget Meeting Dr. [Jules] Kolodny, Dec 21, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9493)
  - Office of Herman Badillo, Jazi [?] Konoshima, Nov 24, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13665)
  - Fred Koray Portraits, Feb 18, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9786)
  - John Dewey HS Fred Koury, Nov 20, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12912)
  - PS 33 Early Childhood Helen Lai, Marilyn Copeland, Apr 8, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12490)
  - Teachers of Year, Board of Education, [Carol] Landau / Frudland, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13586)
  - Carol Landau Bronx, Jan 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12317)
  - PS 102 Para-Professional Carol Landau [?], Feb 4, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13825)
  - PS 136 Bronx Play Carol Landau [?], May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13356)
  - Laretzky [with others], Dec 8, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13713)
  - [Abe] Lefkowitz Library Dedication, Feb 16, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12395)
  - Nina Leichter Portraits, Feb 18, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9696)
  - Leonardi, Salvatore, Jun 23, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11980)
  - Prof. Staff Congress - Kingsboro Comm. College, Sarelik - Ruth Lerner, Mar 27, 1973 (Box 29, Item 14280)
  - District 14 Marshall Levenfer, Feb 6, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11650)
  - Board of Education Abe Levine congratulating I[saiah?] Robinson, new pres[ident] of BOE, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13282)
  - Abe Levine Portrait, Jan 31, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9633)
  - Abe Levine, Elementary Schools - Mr. Alpin, Apr 29, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13251)
  - Board of Education Abe Levine speaking, Apr 26, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13229)
  - City Hall Hearing Abe Levine, Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13867)
  - Abe Levine at City Hall budget hearing, Feb 23, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13090)
  - Group Women Abe Levine, Dec 19, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11573)
  - Abe Levine [headshots], Dec 4, 1969 (Box 30, Item 15597)
  - Abe Levine & Sy Schwartz touring corridor classrooms PS 144 Manhattan, Dec 8, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12943)
  - Abe Levine & speakers at 110 Livingston St., Sep 29, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12784)
  - PS 6 Demonstration Abe Levine [Includes shots of damage to school and Levine being interviewed by WEVD Radio.], Mar 23, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12456)
  - Abe Levine Planning Board, Dec 17, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13744)
  - Abe Levine - first meeting, Oct 5, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13502)
  - Abe Levine - Mortgage - Staten Island, Jan 20, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13803)
  - Childhood Center Abe Levine Brooklyn, Sep 14, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13475)
  - Local School Board Jerry Levine, May 18, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12592)
  - Joe Levine Portraits, Feb 1, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9699)
  - Parsons Jr. H.S., Sol Levine JHS 168, Sylvia Dansy PS 201 [?], Jan 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11615)
  - Sol Levine [headshots], Aug 20, 1971 (Box 30, Item 15603)
  - Tax Committee of Retired Teachers Chapter [Grace Levinson, Edith Goldman (gets help), Mildred Haselkorn, Beulah Lipsky, Leah Isaacs], Mar 11, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11707)
  - Retired Teachers Committee Sylvia Levinson, Marc Ballroom, 16th st., Nov 9, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13613)
  - [New York State] Controller [Arthur] Levitt, May 10, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11207)
  - Raymond Lizza [portrait], Nov 9, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9518)
  - Portraits Raymond Lizza, Sep 30, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13493)
  - PS 33 Manhattan Headshots Mrs. Long, Mrs. Ruiz, Jun 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11968)
  - District 16 Alan B. Lubin, (Eileen Lubin - Stephen Epstein), Feb 28, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11691)
  - Senator [John J.] Marchi, Nov 19, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7992)
  - Alice Marsh Portraits, Dec 2, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9455)
  - Alice Marsh [headshots], May 10, 1970 (Box 30, Item 15601)
  - Const. Convention Alice Marsh, Jun 8, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10552)
  - Teachers' Guild - Luncheon Biltmore [?] (Thurgood Marshall, Dewey Award winner), Mar 2, 1957 (Box 1, Item 3472)
  - Henrietta Mazen Portraits [Collection includes a corresponding print.], Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9866)
  - Dr. [ Mary] Meade, May 27, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11910)
  - [AFT] Mr. [Carl] Megel, Mr. [Charles] Cogen & others, Aug 22, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7822)
  - [AFT] Mr. [Carl] Megel & Mr. [Charles] Cogen & others, Aug 22, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7823)
  - Ruth Melton & Rep. Kelly, Jan 2, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8055)
  - Mrs. [Ruth] Melton - Homebound [teachers], Mar 13, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11712)
  - HS Committee - Bob Miller, Mar 9, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13129)
  - District 6 PS 186 City Hall Rob Miller, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13097)
  - PS 15 Gil Millstern, Apr 6, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14294)
  - Repro Senator Wayne Morse, Feb 3, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9639)
  - Richard Mudgett [headshots], May 16, 1968 (Box 30, Item 15592)
  - District 17 Clara Barton H. S. Lester Weinberg, Ed Muir, Erasmus, Jan 31, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11640)
  - Congressman Murphy - La Perville, Oct 29, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12859)
  - Congressman Murphy Tavern on the Green reception - Staten Island, Oct 30, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12860)
  - QuEST course # 128 Mr. Nancoo of Montreal, Canada, Jan 6, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13784)
  - Fred Nauman -UFT College Scholarships, Feb 4, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13826)
  - Carmella Nefi Luncheon, Apr 29, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13964)
  - Senator Ohrenstein [with others on couches], Dec 9, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13715)
  - District 13 Sands Drive JHS, Pete O'Rourke, Will Farolson [?], Mike Levine, Jan 23, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11612)
  - Sal Pacifico [headshots], Feb 1, 1973 (Box 30, Item 15605)
  - District 27 Tom Pappas, Jan 30, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11642)
  - Richard Parrish, Nov 22, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10165)
  - [Dominica] Sara Mae Peri, Nov 13, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12192)
  - Senator Podell, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13514)
  - Ralph Poynter Portraits [Collection includes a corresponding print.], Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9865)
  - Election District 11 Mario Raimo, Jan 16, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11600)
  - District 5 Candidates, Congressman Rangel, Apr 7, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14296)
  - Mario Ranno - Gershow [?] PS 93, Feb 3, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13824)
  - Lillian Roberts, Dec 13, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11562)
  - Students of School of Art & Design with Pres. Isaiah E. Robinson, Board of Education, Oct 21, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13547)
  - Retirement Bill, Gov. Rockefeller & Gotham Hotel, Apr 29, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12542)
  - Supervisory Retirement Bill [Governor] Rockefeller/Gotham [Hotel], Apr 29, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12542)
  - Mel Rogers, May 28, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10733)
  - Congressman Abe Rosenthal Queens, Mrs. Magidson, Oct 15, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13532)
  - Gladys Roth Para-Professional Brooklyn, Nov 10, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12187)
  - District 29 Herb Magidson, Andrew Jackson HS, Susan Dorreck PS 156, Gloria Weinman PS 176 & Gladys Roth, Jan 21, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11607)
  - Gladys Roth [headshots], Feb 26, 1970 (Box 30, Item 15598)
  - Board of Education Mitchell Rubin Swearing in Retirement Board, May 7, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12561)
  - Rubin, Mitchell Portraits, Jan 14, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9547)
  - Civic Review Board [Bayard] Rustin / Coshells, Nov 2, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10117)
  - Citywide Emergency Committee Bayard Rustin, Feb 2, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13048)
  - Bayard Rustin & Dave's [?] at Board Room & Headshots [talking to Para-Professionals], May 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12610)
  - Philip Saltz [headshots], May 16, 1969 (Box 30, Item 15595)
  - PS 113 Brooklyn District 19 [?] Harold Saltzman Lane HS, Jan 15, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11592)
  - [Dan] Sanders, Jan 23, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10252)
  - District 22 CC Meeting Dan Sanders & Ivan Tiger, Feb 10, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13830)
  - Dan Sanders at Fordham, Apr 20, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13213)
  - HS Students / Dan Sanders [Eugene Kauffman Legal Office / Fern Midwood, Asst. S[?] / Debbie Isom], Mar 10, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11706)
  - [Dan] Sanders, Jun 3, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11930)
  - Bronx Boro Office Congressman Scheuer, Oct 22, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13557)
  - Dr. Schreiber Board of Education HS Committee, Mar 31, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13183)
  - Ecology Program Mr. Schwartz, Sep 30, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13494)
  - District 3 Manhattan Simon Schwartz 4 Group, Jan 14, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11591)
  - Vincent Scialabba, May 28, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10732)
  - Teachers' Guild - head/ group shots [at Guild Headquarters?] Dave Selden on guitar, Dec 27, 1956 (Box 1, Item 3357)
  - Teachers [David] Selden, Nov 27, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6664)
  - [Al] Shanker Reception Bronx, Oct 31, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12132)
  - Child Guidance Group, Check to Albert Shanker + Headshot, Bilingual Teachers, Jan 16, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11597)
  - District 28 Albert Shanker Man of the Year, May 23, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11895)
  - Al] Shanker, [Bayard] Rustin, Jim Howard, Vito DeLeonardis [HTUFT?], Apr 8, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11766)
  - Albert Shanker reception Brooklyn, Nov 13, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12193)
  - Queens reception [Al] Shanker, Nov 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12214)
  - Albert Shanker jail release & reception, May 29, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12629)
  - News Conference [Al] Shanker & Central Labor Council - endorsing Barry Farber Commodore, Oct 26, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12845)
  - Congressman Murphy, Joe Shanahan & [Al] Shanker, Sep 30, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12791)
  - Albert Shanker at PS 11 Bronx Boycott, Sep 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12757)
  - Para-Professionals - [Al] Shanker Meeting, Nov 24, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12231)
  - Boardroom Headquarters - [Al] Shanker, Dec 10, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12957)
  - Rally City Hall - United for Better Schools Shot w/ [Al] Shanker & [Dave] Selden standing on a raised platform, Jun 15, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12681)
  - [Al] Shanker - [Dave] Selden Reception, Jun 9, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12662)
  - Taft HS [Al] Shanker Speaking, Jan 28, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13041)
  - Grapes, Albert Shanker [seated with boxes of "Union Label Table Grapes" in support of United Farmworkers AFL-CIO], Jun 1, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12631)
  - Shanker at Jail, May 15, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12588)
  - [Al] Shanker & Victor Riesel, Mar 23, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12459)
  - JHS 218 Queens Albert Shanker Speech, Jan 27, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13038)
  - Albert Shanker Speaking - Erasmus HS, Feb 9, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13063)
  - Albert Shanker Speaking - Brooklyn Boro Office, Feb 9, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13064)
  - Press Conference - Shanker Para-Professionals, Apr 20, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12523)
  - [Al] Shanker & Sheriff, May 15, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12587)
  - Al] Shanker reception George Washington Hotel, Dec 4, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12251)
  - Walton HS Bronx Shanker Speech, Jan 22, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13028)
  - [Al] Shanker Dinner, Dec 15, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12282)
  - [Al] Shanker, color, undated (Box 30, Item 15608)
  - Chapter Chairmen's Meeting with Albert Shanker, John Hill, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13516)
  - Albert Shanker & H__ [?] s__ [?] __ [?] Marc Ballroom, May 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13352)
  - Board of Education Albert Shanker & [Murray] Bergtraum leaving for Albany, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13280)
  - Central Comm. HS Albert Shanker Speaking, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13217)
  - Gov. Rockefeller & Albert Shanker, Dec 22, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13753)
  - Board of Estimate Albert Shanker Speaking, May 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13347)
  - Press Conference - Albert Shanker, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13521)
  - Albert Shanker Speaking to Bi-Lingual Group Gramercy Park Hotel Tiffany Room, Oct 20, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13546)
  - [Al] Shanker / Rockefeller Press Conference, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13581)
  - Ocean Hill Demonstration City Hall [UFT Pres. Albert Shanker speaking from atop a truck to crowd with umbrellas at City Hall rally during Ocean Hill/Brownsville crisis.], May 24, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11238)
  - Marc Ballroom Chapter Chairman Meeting Albert Shanker Speaking, Dec 15, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13734)
  - Maxwell Vocational HS Wartburg Lutheran Hospital Albert Shanker, Jun 2, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13374)
  - Albert Shanker Speaking to US Civil Rights Comm., Brotherhood Building, Feb 15, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13835)
  - Albert Shanker testimony NY County Lawyers Association, Mar 10, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13885)
  - Retired teachers luncheon Albert Shanker Speaking St. Moritz [?] Hotel, May 9, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13976)
  - Press Conference Shanker - Roberts, May 30, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14034)
  - Spec. Ed. Comm. Albert Shanker, Oct 31, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14475)
  - Shanker, Albert [headshots], Apr 13, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8243)
  - Check Presentation office - Albert Shanker - [Charles] Cogen, Apr 15, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8248)
  - HS Art & Design Albert Shanker Speaking to Students, Nov 5, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13597)
  - Albert Shanker at Einstein School IS 131, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 16, Item 12997)
  - JHS 51 - Albert Shanker Speaking - Staten Island, Mar 17, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13151)
  - Albert Shanker at talking typewriter, Jul 9, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12718)
  - District 30, Joseph Shannon, New Dorp HS, Staten Island, Jan 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11606)
  - District 2 Reception, Dr. Shapiro, Apr 14, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13937)
  - Leo Shapiro [headshots], May 17, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13307)
  - Shapiro, Morris, Nov 21, 1966 (Box 6, Item 10734)
  - Rose Shapiro - gov., Feb 10, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12385)
  - Charles Shebar, May 28, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10729)
  - [Jose] Spinoza [headshots], May 1, 1974 (Box 30, Item 15607)
  - District 6, Jose Spinoza [Whitestone Photos], May 6, 1974 (Box 30, Item 14634)
  - Andrew Stein; Buses and Rally, Sep 16, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11359)
  - [Andrew] Stein w/ Union, Sep 26, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11375)
  - Dorothy Steirmey [?] PS, Mar 21, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11733)
  - Prof. Taft, Jan 31, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13821)
  - Anne Taitt [headshots], Nov 3, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12868)
  - PS 11 Ivan Tiger With Chapter Chairmen & principal visiting classes, Nov 5, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13598)
  - JHS 65 or 46 Manhattan PTA, Ivan Tiger, John Hill, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13520)
  - District 2 Richman H.S. Ivan Tiger, Feb 2, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11641)
  - Ivan Tiger & Justin Finger 260 PAS, Nov 4, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13599)
  - Ben Tobias Portraits, Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9867)
  - Mrs. Turner [headshots], Mar 14, 1968 (Box 30, Item 15591)
  - Headshot + O'Neill Demonstration [signs read "Unionism Yes, Racism No" and "Self-Determination for Black Communities"] [Headshots of Unidentified Individual], Nov 4, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11473)
  - AFT Repro for Mr. H. Caylor [of an unidentified individual], Aug 19, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7818)
  - [Headshots of unidentified woman], Feb 3, 1972 (Box 30, Item 15604)
  - Hughes PS 2 [portraits of unidentified individual], Oct 20, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8613)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Jun 18, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14396)
  - School Rep. Meeting & Headshots Gramercy Sq. Hotel [Unidentified Individuals], Jun 19, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11979)
  - Para-Professionals Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 29, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12149)
  - Headshots Gramercy Hotel [Unidentified Individuals], May 7, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12567)
  - NY Teachers' Guild Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Jan 8, 1958 (Box 1, Item 3940)
  - Teachers' Guild head shots [Unidentified Individuals], Sep 26, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4331)
  - Teachers' Guild 2 Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Dec 26, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4593)
  - United Federation of Teachers [Unidentified Individuals], Sep 28, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5860)
  - Staff Photos [Unidentified Individuals], Feb 17, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9669)
  - Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Dec 28, 1960 (Box 2, Item 6091)
  - Headshots Teachers Assembly [Unidentified Individuals], Mar 5, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8173)
  - Headshots, Central Labor Council, School Board Candidates [Unidentified Individuals], May 7, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12566)
  - [Four unidentified male UFT members], Feb 1, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6147)
  - JHS 275 Brooklyn Senator & Congressman [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 27, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13570)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Mar 9, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13136)
  - Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Nov 10, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10878)
  - Group [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 25, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10860)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13226)
  - Secretaries [Unidentified Individuals], Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13015)
  - Bronx / H.S. [meeting and headshots of unidentified individuals], Dec 8, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12945)
  - School Service Officers [Unidentified Individuals], Dec 3, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12938)
  - PS 66 [Shots of unidentified teachers], Jan 11, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10229)
  - Group Secretaries headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Nov 2, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12866)
  - Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], May 29, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11923)
  - Portrait UFT Officers Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Sep 14, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12750)
  - School Secretaries headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Nov 10, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13618)
  - Secretaries Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 7, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13518)
  - Headshots [Dated 09/03, 04, 08/1970.] [Unidentified Individuals], Sep 3, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12739)
  - Headshots [Unidentified Individuals], Jun 6, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11942)
  - Headshots & Group [Unidentified Individuals], May 24, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10511)
  - IS 318 Food Exhibit Maureen Vidal, Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13654)
  - Early Childhood Chairman Rose de Fuente, Eva Vigman, May 24, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13341)
  - Assemblyman Walsh [speaking to audience], Mar 10, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13892)
  - NYU Professor Weber, Dec 9, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12951)
  - [Moses?] Weinstein headshot, May 3, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8302)
  - PS 215 Brooklyn Dedication to Dr. Morris H. Weiss, Dec 9, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13719)
  - Josh Wiesen Portraits [Collection includes a corresponding print.], Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9868)
  - Swearing in Dave Wittes, May 12, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11861)
  - Teachers Retirement Board Scott/Wittes, Nov 1, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13588)
  - Meeting [David] Wittes, Feb 20, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9675)
  - Dr. Gross, Supt. Swearing in Dr. [ David] Wittes, May 9, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7666)
  - [David] Wittes Portraits [Collection includes two corresponding prints.], Apr 30, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9238)
  - Whitney Young Junior Statler Hilton, Jun 10, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10568)
  - AFT Collective Bargaining Conference Mr. Nicholas Zonarich AFL-CIO, Mr. C. Smith, Gary Story & Panel, undated (Box 3, Item 7821)
- Series XI: Legislative and Government.
  - Board of Education, undated (Box 30, Item 15609)
  - Board of Education Public Schools Reading Clubs, Jan 30, 1956 (Box 1, Item 2802)
  - Board of Education, Oct 26, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6595)
  - Board of Education, Dec 21, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6720)
  - Bargaining at Board of Education, Feb 6, 1962 (Box 2, Item 6846)
  - City Council, Mar 6, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8175)
  - Board of Education, Dec 7, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8694)
  - Board of Education Contract Signing, Jan 25, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8813)
  - Board of Education, Sep 6, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11329)
  - Board of Education, Oct 16, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11426)
  - Hollis, Board of Education Fantasy [?] East Para-Professionals, May 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11885)
  - Board of Education Sid Harris, Jun 10, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11956)
  - Board of Education, Nov 7, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12179)
  - Board of Education Early Childhood com [?], Nov 17, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12202)
  - Board of Education Contract Signing [?], Dec 16, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12286)
  - Church [?] Brooklyn Local School Boards, Jan 10, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12322)
  - Board of Estimate Hearing, Feb 26, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12407)
  - Retirement Bill, Gov. Rockefeller & Gotham Hotel, Apr 29, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12542)
  - Supervisory Retirement Bill [Governor] Rockefeller/Gotham [Hotel], Apr 29, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12542)